Ouch!
Brother, here's your phone
Clean up here
Ha, call the police
Ah, that, brother.
The gambling house was reported to the National Intelligence Service.
I was robbed, Mr...
When?
Just now, the fucking guy...
Why are you talking about that now?
Oh, you idiot, really, Mr.
Don't move!
Get out of the way
Get out of the way!
Hey, get out of here.
Factory closed for the time being
- Yes
- Uh
Now, air raid alert level 1 has been issued.
Just like I trained
Moves quickly and accurately
I'm losing
attacked by these robbers
I am the store owner
illegal gambling house
You can see at a glance on the monitor
Is there a system in place?
Oh, above?
That's my place of business too.
여기 연결된 곳이지예
아이, 씹새끼들이, 그냥, 아이
아이
지원 요청하고
관련 증거 싹 다 뒤져
네
어
거, 빨리 요청해
아
왜 이래!
- Be quiet.
- Oh, I'm the store owner.
Boy, fuck, really
Ah, on the day of the stage game
I turn off all the surrounding CCTV.
What should I do?
Embroider yourself
Well, my brother ordered it.
So?
Are you going to involve me in it?
Brother, I really did this time
Don’t you know that this is a promotion case?
To the bag behind my brother
What do you want me to do?
A hundred behind me?
Who is that bag?
That's it, I don't know.
VIP-level people around...
Ana, this bastard
Look at your tongue becoming lighter
This guy, this, huh?
It's expired, this one
sorry
I will suspend you for 6 months.
Go to the audit team and voluntarily pay your taxes, huh?
why?
Not satisfied?
no
thank you for your concern
- Yeah, huh?
- Yes
cub
please speak
I think Han Soo-hyun knows that place.
I didn't know
I contacted you several times.
Ha, yeah?
yes
Okay
Now let's get started
Let’s eat too
I might cry all night today
Hey, eat more quickly.
How much did I testify yesterday?
I don't eat, I don't eat, I don't eat!
Even if you say let's eat and eat,
Why are you extreme?
Hey, get it out of here.
Are burgers important now?
‘Jay went to Jang Jung-hyuk’s hideout.
'Go find it'
He even said, ‘I submitted a proposal.’
Okay, and then what?
Have you had a good life? uh?
I told you I'd come back, right?
IC
Almost my precious database
Almost flew away, shit, shit
You said you started working again?
Hey, how many years has it been?
Has it been 5 years?
I have to subtract 3 years
3 years of rotten bread because of you
Money laundering?
Then I won't need it
But why did you come?
Did you come because you wanted to see it?
Ah, like this
You're spilling it out
You won't miss me, huh?
Hey, when is the Hong Kong dollar
You mastered it, huh?
Hey
What do you think?
What if you do it right with me?
'Properly?'
what do you mean?
Does this mean you won't stab me in the back this time?
Does this mean you won’t kill people?
uh?
not me
No? warehouse explosion
You're not?
Ah, this, really me, this
How can I do it like back then?
Will you accept my offer?
That happened 5 years ago
If I said I did it, would you do it?
Then I'll admit it
Whether it's a hundred times or a thousand times
as much as you want
With those words, quietly
Don't think about moving on
Be honest
tell me the truth
'True?'
Then will you believe it?
To tell the truth
not me
It's shameless
After doing such a terrible thing
Come to me as if nothing happened
Want to work with me?
You know what?
If we do this together
Resolving that misunderstanding
don't talk nonsense
Then it's up to you
Added interest to the bank for 5 years
It's Bitcoin, it's NFT
In a world where real money is disappearing
Counterfeiting work coming soon
It will disappear into romance
Your skills too
It will disappear into memories
Finally, try to do it right.
counterfeit dream
To Supernote
Soohyun
Come see me tomorrow
Huh?
I can't even recognize my partner
If I had been hit, it would have really been a goal.
Why didn't you tell me in advance that Jay was coming?
Oh, I didn't have time to contact you.
Yeon and Suhyeon
Are we moving together?
Oh, what is that kid?
Of course, I move with Suhyun.
Yeon is that girl
I thought you had high-level hacking skills, but
Even the virtual currency wallet is stolen.
I didn't know it was a skill
In order for this plan to succeed
Because I really need this skill
Make sure to come out tomorrow
Wow
Brother, don’t you trust me?
I'm a fixer
제가 무조건 나오게 할 테니까
걱정하지 마세요
어우, 진짜, 쯧
못 믿는다, 새끼야
어떻게 믿냐?
Boy, really, Mr.
Ha, indeed
It’s been a while, Han Soo-hyun
Get out of the car!
- Get out of the car!
- Valet
Oh, please close that door and come in.
Who is this?
These days, banknote serial numbers are also used
Identify the picture
To get a serial number
Go to the Mint Corporation server
I have to hack it
Yeoni
I'm a hacker who understands
I only trust Suhyun
I was about to start work, hey
Please take care of me
I will listen to the plan and decide.
So?
whose portrait
Are you going to make a supernote?
Mrs. Saimdang
- How much?
- 1 million copies
'1 million copies?'
- What about distribution?
- 50 billion counterfeit bills
I bought drugs worth 200 billion won.
To the Colombian and Mexican mafia
We will resell them for 100 billion each.
Detailed questions
You can do it with a fixer.
What is my share of them?
Excluding material and processing costs
Divide 200 billion 6 to 4
Of course I'm 6
6 to 4 sides...
Multiply 200 billion by 4 and divide by 10
400...
billion
wow
Call!
Call, call
Swallowing 120 billion alone
Should we share it among the rest of us?
why?
no?
You know, this job.
Planning and distribution rather than production
It's more important
Oh no, no, no, good
I love sharing
How long do you schedule?
2 weeks of setting up
10 weeks of production, three months in total
But someone important is missing?
intaglio printing press
Without it, you can't make a supernote.
Iron Curtain Gangsuni Nui
You mean it has to be there?
I tried to look for it several times
I can't contact you
That sister 5 years ago
Because I was making an intaglio printing press.
It should have been completed by now.
Did you cut this?
What if I cut it like this?
Do you know how much this piece of paper costs?
A son who is starving in your homeland
It's enough money to buy a meal
This piece of paper
It's like life.
Get your mind straight!
Wow, that's a lot of dirty talk.
Have you been to Aoji?
I am someone who has been to Aoji twice.
Have you ever killed someone?
If you've never killed someone before, don't be crazy.
Is Park Gwang-soon here?
Who are you?
My name is Park Kwang-soon, right?
Win, win, give up
It’s been a while, Aunt Kangsuni.
Have you had a good life?
But
Loosen up on that asshole
Who do you call me, such a troublesome brat?
me?
Can you see it?
Like that, like that
They say that kid has no brain.
What did I request?
Come here
Please come in
Now
No, you're going in here?
Be careful
Wow
Oh!
Even though I lived this difficult life
Without wasting a single penny of your investment
It's all here
I poured it out
Hey
Are you making money with this?
Awesome
Is it good?
aunt
Serial number hacking successful
Huh?
new serial number
I won 10 million
Enter it into the Mint Corporation server.
yes
How is it going?
Hey, I won 11 million
Let’s share 1 million with me.
Sister, how are you doing?
Now there are five stripes on both ends of the bill
The fine characters hidden in the plum tree
It is a raised print.
Anti-counterfeiting elements
It completely blocks it.
It started working
- Drink!
- Ta-da!
Wow, Mr...
Supernote 50 billion won
The day I filmed everything
Yeon goes to a wine bar with Jay.
He begged me to have a party
I
All the cash in my wallet without Jay knowing.
I exchanged it for a fresh counterfeit bill.
It's 2.75 million won.
2.75 million won
Yeah
Okay?
Counterfeit bills are released into the market
I called to report it.
identify yourself
Do you have any intention?
No, just
I will remain as an anonymous reporter.
The identity of the informant is
We provide thorough protection
This will give credibility to the report.
If you go to the address I gave you
You will be able to check it right away.
Where did it come from? huh?
It was perfect, so
can fool everyone
I thought there would be
But
I called the National Intelligence Service to report
Jay knows I did it
Yeon and I were locked up.
That's difficult
The supernote was also completed.
At least it’s like a time bomb
I guess I don't need you anymore
no
They said they would change their distribution plan.
Yeon risked his life
Made me do more work
What more did you ask me to do?
What is the changed plan?
I took more supernotes.
9 million copies
If you add up to the 50 billion initially made,
gun
500 billion?
What next?
What happened next?
The day when 500 billion counterfeit bills were completed
Suddenly moved to a new hideout
Yeon burned it too
Where?
Is it a container?
Yeah
burn quickly
- Go
- Yes
Soohyun Han
stay here
Clean up after yourself
You say you do whatever you ask, huh?
Hey, lock it.
and
Called to the port the next day and bread?
Ha, you couldn't trust me anymore
Because I got what I wanted
There's no need
It's me
Now there are 500 billion counterfeit bills
It's solved, right?
Still
Copperplate and intaglio printing press
If you have these two
You can take unlimited supernotes.
Ha, I'm going crazy
No, then what happens to the call volume?
What will happen to prices?
I know what you mean.
But
That's all I know
Listen carefully
You and Yeon
I'll erase it from your case record.
And after you come to Korea
Arrangements are made
What do you think?
Because of that bastard
Bread rotted for 3 years
think about it carefully
It's a kite
Shall we talk?
Where are you being taken, sister?
It's a kite
You know that Soo-hyun went to the National Intelligence Service.
Is your sister in the National Intelligence Service?
I don't know?
Do you really not know?
Ah...
I have to believe it when they say it’s not, well.
Ah, to Suhyun.
There was a small accident
So the police showed up
Ah, but Suhyun
Cha Ki-tae to the National Intelligence Service
I heard you asked me to meet you?
uh?
why
Uh, you have no reason to do that.
Call the National Intelligence Service to report a tip
Because I got caught and was cornered
I went in there all the way, all on my own.
no
Anyway...
This time too, like 5 years ago
Only Suhyun writes alone.
I'm going to prison
Oh no
Behind Jang Jung-hyuk
There is great power
So Cha Ki-tae, who was investigating, got drunk.
Han Soo-hyun wrote it alone.
But this time
I
I will use that great power
Under the condition of dividing 500 billion in half.
for our personal protection
I'm going to ask you to take responsibility.
For that personal protection,
Of course, Han Soo-hyun is also included.
I
Are you going to believe that literally?
If you don't believe it
Are you just going to leave it as is?
You don't have to do anything
Soohyun
I can pull it out safely.
To do that, your ability
Totally necessary
If you kick it a little higher
It is possible to regain first place.
I'm out of bullets
There are only three months left
It's a big deal
Funds just yesterday
You said it as if everything would be corrected.
- What is this?
-Something happened suddenly.
in another way
I'm pulling tight
Please work hard
No, not corporate money.
It's not a slush fund
Candidates from both parties eat it too
The funds that are completely unobstructed
Made by deep-frying gujeongmul
Don't you know that it's money?
Rep. Choi
Yes?
There is no harm in taking it away
Just pick the criminal's money
Shuking this thing
Is this something that not everyone can do?
I know, I know.
You don’t even know my hard work, really.
I'm sorry
please try a little harder
Because I'm telling you
don't be upset
Take responsibility this time
Because I will complete my mission
Entering the first financial sector is a must, right?
Even in both parties
You are well aware of Chairman Bang’s hard work.
I get scabs in my ears too
'Cause I keep pumping
don't worry
suddenly
You can't provide funds
Because of the Incheon illegal gambling house incident?
yes
More than 70% of capital production
It was a factory occupied by
Because of that
Suddenly the operation stopped
Is it him again? The guy who caused the accident?
지검장님이
좀 나서 주셔야겠습니다
뭐, 어젯밤에 연락받고
응급 조치를 취하긴 했는데
참 나, 요즘 세상이 어떤 세상인데
그거 미친 새끼 아니에요?
Still
On the money production side
creating something from nothing
He's a very outstanding guy.
No matter how excellent he is
If you keep crossing the line like this
I can't help it
I have to cut it out
If we do something wrong, we will get hurt.
I will ask you to do so.
After being quiet for a few years
It was an anxious car, but oh my.
Did you do a really good job this time?
Oh, I wish I could raise my status
To match that
Don’t you have to live?
About each person's way of life
condition of not touching
In the contract we signed 10 years ago
I know it's stated
yes
After meeting you, I joined the Eulhoe Society.
The guy who ran a loan business with Yakuza money
swallowed up eight savings banks
Became the head of a third-party financial group
It means that everything has arrived now.
The first financial sector will soon
The position of CEO of Woorim Financial Group is
It's glimmering right in front of my nose.
So be careful, be careful
Let's be careful again
Don't just act according to your nature,
There will be no end to this incident
You solved it well, right?
District Prosecutor Park already administered first aid.
I decided to take care of everything.
Ah, this by the way
The biggest source of funding
It's a big problem because the factory has stopped.
No need to hide and run the factory
Even if you don’t meet dangerous kids
Even if you just hold your form
300 billion won
It's a big business proposal, take a look.
Hey, is this possible?
Read slowly and ask questions
I'll give you plenty of time
Now Jay, this guy
Supernote 500 billion
It will be released on the market
We are defenseless like this
I'm just wasting time, Mr.
Jay's 500 billion distribution plan
Ha, what on earth?
To Jang Jung-hyuk
By calling
The guy who insists on meeting me
There's only you in the world, man
As you can see, it is written
I guess you've been waiting for my call for a while?
The proposal I gave you is in your head
Bang bang, bang bang, are you wandering around?
It's sick, oh my
Pretend to be strong even if you die soon, Mr.
Follow me
documentary proposal
I'll show you
Ah, the weather is nice
Thank you for your hard work